Lewiston is great with all
these silver sugar masters.
Every shop is lovely. On that.
Note, you're not done shopping.
If you go to more shops,
will your scarecrow head
get any less empty?
How rude.
It's not every day I come
to Lewiston. One more shop.
What? Uh, go to shop.
That's right. What a.
Shame.
I'll family shop is the one
I wanted to see the most.
Watson helping Lee.
Someone I admire.
People say he's talented
enough to stand toe to toe with
the silver sugar Viscount. Oh.
Westerlies north of here, so
it might be even colder there.
If you're worried about it,
then just don't go.
No, that's not an option
since they have
so many silver
sugar masters here,
nobody will pay me any mind.
But in Westall even I might find
some success.
Huh? Is this a confectionery?
I don't know, it doesn't
really look like one. No.
I know. Let's go find out. Ah
ah.
So she's attempting to fill
up her scarecrow head again.
This is exquisite.
I wonder who created it.
Hey! You there? Quit sleeping.
Who's that? It is I, the world
famous Mithra lit pod. Huh?
Did you say silly fish rod or
cod?
All right. You're not funny.
Now, now,
don't be rude, mithril.
Yeah.
What's all the ruckus?
Yeah. Oh, dear.
What have you done,
you little pipsqueak? Huh?
Wait, you mean me? Spare me
the act. Hold on a minute.
Who are you? I don't blame her.
It was the man in the.
Black robe you should be mad at.
Benjamin, explain.
What I just told you. There was
a man in black
standing right there.
Why the commotion?
Is something wrong?
Right. I remember he was dressed
in black like that.
You mean this fairy is responsible?
For what, pray tell?
No, he didn't do anything.
He's our
travel companion and only
came into the shop just now.
Uh.
It's you. Aren't you the girl
who was asked
to approach the king
at the last contest? Um, yes.
Mhm. Good.
Then get to work. What?
To pay back what you just did.
Hey, I said it wasn't me.
Good. Then there's no need
to work. Let's go.
Not till I've been compensated.
Will not make me kill you.
Oh, I'd like to see you try.
Fine.
So please don't start a fight.
Huh huh huh huh huh huh.
It's my choice and I'm
going to work here.
So both of you, please let go.
Are you sure? Excellent.
No taking it back now.
Why would you do this?
It won't take me long
to make one sugar confection.
Besides, maybe I can
learn something new, right?
I'd like to see how
he makes such lovely things.
You're going to pay
for something you didn't do.
Yes.
It could be a great opportunity.
All right.
I'll work you to the bone,
you little brat.
Remember, you owe me. Mm mm mm.
Hurry up, pipsqueak.
Disorder is due in two days.
My name is an mr. Cat.
I prefer pipsqueak, and you'd
better stop making fun of me.
I'm not making fun of you.
You're
calling me a cat?
That's terribly rude.
Adding Mr. to that foul
nickname. It's awful.
Oh, so Cat is your nickname.
What
parents would be so irresponsible to name
their son after an animal?
Some idiot's started calling
me that. And now
almost everyone thinks
it's my real name.
Hey, Mr. Cat. Um.
Yes, Mr. glowing personality.
You don't have any sugar
confections on display.
So is this a real business?
Is there
actually a buyer for
the one you're making now?
Huh? Thanks for your concern,
but I managed
to put food on the table.
And yes, this order is intended
for a wedding ceremony.
Interesting. How much is it? 59.
That's all. But why? It could
sell for a lot more than that.
Because I don't make
things for just anyone.
Sadly, the customers
I accept can't always afford it.
This sugar confection
is for a cobbler's daughter,
and 59 is still
a high price for her.
All these sugar artisans.
Why are they such idiots?
Silver. Sugar. We're fresh out.
I'd have had plenty
to work with if it weren't
for a certain someone.
I started refining another
big batch of it,
but it won't be ready
until tomorrow morning.
Then I guess we'll have to wait.
But will that be enough?
Sure, we'll be fine.
Well, let's call it a day.
Be ready tomorrow.
Are.
I don't know. What if that's
not enough silver sugar?
It's called.
Huh?
Why are you awake
at this late hour?
Don't startle me like that.
Goodness.
What are you doing?
Did I wake you? I'm sorry.
I came to see where you were.
I thought maybe I should just refine
another barrel. Thank you. Shell.
Did Cat tell you to do this?
No, but it looks like
we barely have enough.
I'd feel terrible if we ran out.
So.
You're obsessed. Our sugar confections. All
that you think about.
There's no need to poke fun.
Are you cold? Yes.
Fairies don't really feel the cold,
though. Isn't that right? Right.
Lord know it. What about warmth?
A little bit, yes.
The sensation somewhat like
touching something fluffy. Levy.
It's hard to imagine.
Ciao. What are you doing?
Does it help?
Make you warmer. Yes. But I.
Thank you. Shall.
I'm better now. All right.
Where'd all this come from?
I prepared more just in case.
The portion that I sent
out to dry
yesterday is ready to be meled.
So we can get to work now.
Hmm'hmm. Huh?
Hello? Hey.
Did you eat breakfast?
Not yet. Then go eat something
first. Artisans need their energy.
Yes, sir. Go ahead. Benjamin.
We'll do.
The.
Stop, Peg.
You can't go that way.
Through you little. Don't go in there.
This is a sacred workspace.
What brings you here?
Viscountess Clay. I heard
that you're working
on a fabulous sugar
confection for the daughter
of a cobbler.
I'm willing to pay you 100
cress. So if you'll just let me.
Have it for the final time,
I refuse to sell to you. What?
You sold many pieces to my servants.
Why not for my daughter?
Think carefully about the way you and
your daughter treat those servants.
Even His Majesty himself couldn't convince me
to do business with you.
But money is no object.
Leave my shop.
You've got some nerve. Oh, my,
what a beautiful fairy you are.
Tell me, is this your fairy?
I would like to buy him.
I'll pay 300.
He belongs to no one.
And who's this little girl?
Off you go.
Trollop. Trollop!
Please leave. Oh, I never.
She just barged into my workshop.
We should purify this place.
Hey. Man.
Look at me through a leopard.
I know that scar. He destroyed
the sugar confection.
Ah, so he does exist. Bold of.
Him to come back here.
No. Matter what happens. I can't
let them touch Kat's work again.
We finished just in time.
It's so beautiful.
And I can already
tell whoever receives.
Confection is going
to have the best of.
Luck, I hope so. The wedding is
tomorrow. Deliver it then. Me?
Are you sure? So you can see
the look on the person's face.
That's the reward for
your hard work. Pip squeak.
Great. Don't be late.
Right. Hey, Benjamin.
Heat up the bath. Will do.
Stop right there.
I knew you'd show up. God!
There's nowhere to run.
Hey, what's with all the noise?
It's you.
I'll try this way. Catch it.
Huh? Oh, hell. Oh, hell. What?
Why are you two.
Are. So.
Where's the real one? Curse you!
I see the night
we finished would be
the best chance to steal it.
Right.
That's why I delivered
the piece before dinner.
Then I set up the fake one
and waited
for the thief to appear.
Who was that man? He's one
of Lady Clay's servants.
She probably ordered
him to steal it.
That means you really didn't
destroy the first one, huh?
I'm sorry this wasn't
fair to you.
It's all right. I discovered something
really valuable in the end.
When she saw the piece,
that girl was so happy.
It's almost like working
here was the tuition
I paid to learn how
much joy that would give me.
Remind me you're going to Westhall
after this, correct? Yes.
I've gotten sick
of the winters in Lewiston.
I'm going to pack this place
up and move south.
Well, cats don't like the cold,
so that only makes sense.
Why do you take
every opportunity to say
something rude to me?
It brings me joy.
I don't understand you,
and I don't
think I want to. Hey, Benjamin.
Yes, sir.
Take my winter clothes. What? I
can't accept something this nice.
Come on. You don't have to be
a polite little
lady about everything.
It's lovely. It's just something this grand
would look strange on me.
It'll look amazing on you
in another five years, though.
I can't picture that.
Well, I can.
You're gonna become even cuter
than you are now. Precisely.
You've got a good eye, don't
you? Oh, I can't give you this.
That pouch.
Yeah, it's got my wing in it.
Why would it be in there?
Because Kat always puts it somewhere
and forgets where it is.
That's why I keep it in here
so it doesn't get lost again.
Why doesn't he just
carry it with him?
Like a lot of people do?
He forgets to.
He only thinks about work,
so it doesn't cross his mind.
Then you could just leave here.
He wouldn't know.
I could if I wanted to. I've
seen lots of humans in my life.
And cats. The most interesting
one to watch. I'm happy.
Here.
Mei, you've lived a really long.
Time, haven't you, Benjamin?
Yes. So I stopped
counting after about 250 years.
So.
Thanks for everything.
Oh, by the way,
do you know
the silver sugar Viscount?
You might run
into him in Westhall.
Oh, does. That mean that you
and Hugh know each other?
Yes. We trained together a long time
ago at the Mercury Workshop.
I got bored and left,
though, after
I became a silver sugar master.
What are you telling me? You've
been given a royal medal. Huh?
You really aren't too bright,
are you?
I mean,
there aren't any silver sugar
masters named cat in this town.
So I've told you countless times. Cat
is just an unfortunate nickname.
And that dim witted reprobate
is the one who gave it to me.
Anyway,
my real name is Alf Hingley.
He moved his shop. That's right.
What a shame.
I'll family shop
is the one I wanted
to see the most.
What's in helping.
Someone. I admire?
You're that elf, Hengly.
So the old man
just meant that you
were planning to move.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I just realized that. So when
I look up to has been calling
me pipsqueak and brat.
Look up to. You're an artisan
too, so never idolize others.
You're one of a kind
and second to none.
I feel like. What Hugh
said to me was similar,
that I shouldn't
imitate someone else.
Thank you, Cat and farewell.
I'll work hard in Westall to.
Would you
like a sugar confection? I'll
even make a custom
order for you.
You said you'd
have better chances here.
Listen to me. Shout and shout.
Just because she hasn't.
Sold a single sugar confection doesn't
mean. Is stupid. All right.
Oh. It's cold again today.